answershark.com 2017-02-26

# Privacy Policy | Answershark.com

This policy explains what kind of data we collect when you use our website, and governs data collection, processing and usage. By using this website, you consent to the data practices described in this policy. For the purposes of the Data Protection Act 1998 ( **Act** ), the data controller is Teaching Writing Online Limited ( **TWO Ltd** ).

We, TWO Ltd, take the privacy of your information seriously and would like our customers to familiarize themselves with all the statements below.

## Data We Collect from You

While using our website, you may be asked to provide to us and we may collect and process personally identifiable information, such as your name, email address, home or work address or telephone number, and other contact information ( **personal information** ). We may also collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your postal code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favourites.

Apart from personal information, information about your computer hardware and software and other statistical data also may be automatically collected by us when you use our website. This may include your IP address, access date and time and referring website addresses, the browser you use, time zone, and information about how and when you use our website. This information is used by us to operate our service, maintain quality of the services and also helps us to improve our services, customize the content of the website and provide general statistics regarding use of the website.

We do not collect, use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

## Use of Personal Information

We collect and use your personal information to operate our website, deliver the services you have requested, and contact you when needed.

We do not disclose, sell, rent or lease your personal information to third parties.

We may share personal information and other data collected from you with our affiliates, trusted partners and contractors exclusively for the purposes of operation and maintenance of the website, provision of the services to you, and communication with you.

We may also use your personal information to inform you of other products or services available from our affiliates and us. We may also contact you to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered, although you do not have to respond to such requests.

We may share data with our affiliates and trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for the services provision. We may share your information with third parties who perform tasks required to complete a purchase transaction. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to us, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

## Storage of Personal Information

As part of the services offered to you through the website, the information you provide to us may be transferred to and stored in countries outside of the European Economic Area ( **EEA** ). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or one of our service providers, contractors or suppliers. If we transfer or store your information outside the EEA, we will take steps with the aim of ensuring that your privacy rights continue to be protected as outlined in this Privacy Policy. If you use our services while you are outside the EEA, your information may be transferred outside the EEA in order to provide you with these services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing by us.

Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk.

## About Cookies

Our website uses cookies and similar technologies to help you personalize and improve your user online experience. A cookie is a small file that is sent to your computer when you visit our website and identifies your computer as you visit our website again. Please note that a cookie file is not capable of identifying a specific user and is used to identify a computer and a browser that was previously used.

There are several things that cookie files help us do: remember that a user is signed in, display date and time according to the current time zone a user is in, and customize the content of our website for a particular user.

Please note that third parties may also use cookies, over which we have no control.  These cookies are likely to be analytical/performance cookies or targeting cookies.

We may use any of the following cookies:

  * Strictly necessary cookies. These are cookies that are required for the operation of our website. They include, for example, cookies that enable you to log into secure areas of our website, use a shopping cart or make use of e-billing services.
  * Analytical/performance cookies. They allow us to recognise and count the number of visitors and to see how visitors move around our website when they are using it. This helps us to improve the way our website works, for example, by ensuring that users are finding what they are looking for easily.
  * Functionality cookies. These are used to recognise you when you return to our website. This enables us to personalise our content for you, greet you by name and remember your preferences (for example, your choice of language or region).
  * Targeting cookies. These cookies record your visit to our website, the pages you have visited and the links you have followed. We will use this information to make our website and the advertising displayed on it more relevant to your interests. We may also share this information with third parties for this purpose.

If you decide to modify cookie settings, you can do so by changing the settings of your browser. However, if you disable cookies entirely, we cannot guarantee that all the features of our website will run smoothly.

## Security

In order to protect your personal information, we use encryption when you send us your personal data. We also take all necessary measures to secure your personal information from loss, unauthorized access, misuse, disclosure, or alteration.

In case there is an intrusion in our system that affects your personal information, we will contact you as soon as possible and notify you of actions we take in response.

## Disclosure

We do not share your personal information with organizations, individuals, and any third parties. However, we will disclose or share your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) comply with any laws, regulations, legal requirements or comply with legal processes; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of TWO Ltd; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the website, or the general public. This includes requests from governmental and public authorities within or outside your country.

We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006.

We may disclose your personal information to third parties: (a) in the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets; and (b) if TWO Ltd or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.

## Links Disclaimer

Our website may contain links to third-party websites, products, and services. Please note that a link does not constitute an endorsement of the content, products, accuracy, services, opinions, viewpoint, policies, or accessibility of that website. Information that these third-party websites may collect from you is governed by their privacy policy.

## Your Rights

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes.  You can exercise your right to prevent such processing at any time by contacting our support team at [support@answershark.com](mailto:support@answershark.com).

## Access to Personal Information

We want you to be sure that personal information that we have collected from you is correct and up-to-date. The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. We will grant you access to your personal information in accordance with the Act so that you are able to update or delete it. To request access to your personal information, you can contact our support team anytime.

## Changes

We will occasionally update our Privacy Policy to reflect customer feedback. For that reason, we may change our Privacy Policy from time to time. Whenever this happens, you will be notified about the changes we have made on this page. That is why we recommend you to visit this page from time to time to be aware of all the changes we might make to our Privacy Policy.

 _ **Last updated** : 04/26/2016_
